<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JakartaOne in Spanish 2020 on JakartaOne Live | Jakarta EE Software | Cloud Native</title>
    <link>https://jakartaone.org/2020/hispano/</link>
    <description>Recent content in JakartaOne in Spanish 2020 on JakartaOne Live | Jakarta EE Software | Cloud Native</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>webdev@eclipse-foundation.org (Christopher Guindon)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>webdev@eclipse-foundation.org (Christopher Guindon)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 15:50:25 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jakartaone.org/2020/hispano/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Speaker Agreement and Recording Waiver</title>
      <link>https://jakartaone.org/2020/hispano/speaker-agreement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>webdev@eclipse-foundation.org (Christopher Guindon)</author>
      <guid>https://jakartaone.org/2020/hispano/speaker-agreement/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ll Give the Talk I agree to present my talk at the conference and to adhere to the content and intent as outlined in the description provided to the program committee.
I&#39;m Responsible I acknowledge that I alone am responsible for the published description of my talk. I will use the website to correct any errors in facts, formatting, grammar, spelling, etc.
No Warranties I provide my material &amp;ldquo;as is,&amp;rdquo; without warranties or conditions of any kind, either expressed or implied including, without limitation, any warranty of fitness for any particular purpose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Committee Members</title>
      <link>https://jakartaone.org/2020/hispano/program-committee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>webdev@eclipse-foundation.org (Christopher Guindon)</author>
      <guid>https://jakartaone.org/2020/hispano/program-committee/</guid>
      <description>Alberto Salazar Entrepreneur, passionate Consultant, Java Champion, Oracle Groundbreaker Ambassador, JUG Leader, Auth0 Ambassador, founder of the Ecuador Java User Group, Java Community Process Associate Member and Java evangelist/trainer; active in twitter at @betosalazar. He is the co-author of the book &#39;Software Architecture with Spring 5.0&#39;. Alberto has been working for 2 decades creating large scalable and high transaction load systems from military software to banking solutions. He is also a frequent speaker at Java conferences such as Oracle Code One, JBCNConf, Voxxed Days, Oracle Code, Red Hat Summit, JavaOne, Oracle Developer Tour Latam, OTN Tours, and local JUG meetings.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>