<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brazil 2020 on JakartaOne Live - September 10, 2019 | Jakarta EE Software | Cloud Native</title>
    <link>https://jakartaone.org/brazil2020/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Brazil 2020 on JakartaOne Live - September 10, 2019 | Jakarta EE Software | Cloud Native</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>webdev@eclipse-foundation.org (Christopher Guindon)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>webdev@eclipse-foundation.org (Christopher Guindon)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 15:50:25 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jakartaone.org/brazil2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Speaker Agreement and Recording Waiver</title>
      <link>https://jakartaone.org/brazil2020/speaker-agreement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>webdev@eclipse-foundation.org (Christopher Guindon)</author>
      <guid>https://jakartaone.org/brazil2020/speaker-agreement/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ll Give the Talk I agree to present my talk at the conference and to adhere to the content and intent as outlined in the description provided to the program committee.
I&#39;m Responsible I acknowledge that I alone am responsible for the published description of my talk. I will use the website to correct any errors in facts, formatting, grammar, spelling, etc.
No Warranties I provide my material &amp;ldquo;as is,&amp;rdquo; without warranties or conditions of any kind, either expressed or implied including, without limitation, any warranty of fitness for any particular purpose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://jakartaone.org/brazil2020/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>webdev@eclipse-foundation.org (Christopher Guindon)</author>
      <guid>https://jakartaone.org/brazil2020/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>All attendees, speakers, sponsors, and volunteers at our conference are required to agree with the following code of conduct.
Organizers will enforce this code throughout the event. We are expecting cooperation from all participants to help ensure a safe environment for everybody.
The Quick Version Our conference is dedicated to providing a harassment-free conference experience for everyone, regardless of gender, sexual orientation, disability, physical appearance, body size, race, or religion. We do not tolerate harassment of conference participants in any form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Committee Members</title>
      <link>https://jakartaone.org/brazil2020/program-committee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>webdev@eclipse-foundation.org (Christopher Guindon)</author>
      <guid>https://jakartaone.org/brazil2020/program-committee/</guid>
      <description>Otavio Santana Empowering developers worldwide to deliver better software faster, scalable in the Cloud. Otavio is a passionate software engineer focused on Cloud and Java technology. He has experience mainly in persistence polyglot and high-performance applications in finances, social media, and e-commerce.
Otavio is a member of both Expert Groups and Expert Leader in several JSRs and JCP executive committee. He is working on several Apache and Eclipse Foundation projects such as Apache Tamaya, MicroProfile, Jakarta EE, where he is leading the first specification at Jakarta EE with Jakarta NoSQL.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>